{
    "id": "7dc2e0c42a1549b88245994b07da57d1",
    "title": "Few vs. Little",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He was not a popular guy. He had very ........................... friends.",
            "description": "Few means almost none. It can be used with very.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e8819ca8108d42cc85def81dd959d743"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have met him only ........................... times.",
            "description": "A few indicates a small number.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "18e2c7d172d341a5b6652c6bce7471aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have ............................. money. We can't eat out tonight.",
            "description": "Little means almost nothing.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "a few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f6ff92aa62b242d0a01abfbcc7a0f97d"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are ............................ apples in the fridge if you are hungry.",
            "description": "A few indicates a small number.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0ed6294a0c84437e8dc2ed17510cc78e"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was ............................. oil in the tank. It was almost empty.",
            "description": "Little oil means almost no oil.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4c6363b7256e49b3a86de8e7f8dd4abb"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has .......................... patience.",
            "description": "Little patience means almost no patience.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "a few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4c960de7fd744cbf95121387c4e8c9dd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have got ............................ money so you can buy that shirt if you want.",
            "description": "A little indicates a small amount.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "a few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6c0c15c30c1e4bb088060a6092f5f9ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "Only ................................ politicians are honest.",
            "description": "Only a few means the same as few.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6069bf8949c1475ea521c4f75e73f89f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ate ................................ food and then went to bed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a few",
                "a little",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "92834f8c240a4a4ebe64cdc37a7969c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I got only .............................. answers correct.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4821501cda8f4127acc39f3a99ec80c5"
        },
        {
            "question": ".......................... people can afford a cruise holiday. It is very expensive.",
            "description": "Only a few means the same as few.",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "A little",
                "Only a few"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "aefaa624f2034c40af8a016e2fb5bce2"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are very ............................... people that I really respect.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ad75589aef4c4db0849c9e1249d1417f"
        }
    ]
}